freshbitesdaily.com 2014-12-20

# Privacy Policy

_**Join the conversation with our positive and enthusiast community on Facebook[here](https://www.facebook.com/FreshBitesDaily).**_

Thank you for visiting our web site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used. Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

We collect NO personally identifiable information on you.

_Cookie/Tracking Technology_  
However, this site uses cookies and tracking technology called Google Analytics. Cookies and Google Analytics tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site, and understanding how visitors use the site. Cookies also help customize the site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies, however if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with Google Analytics to provide us with site management statistics. 

_Distribution of Information_  
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. We will not share your data with any other company outside of these limitations.

_Changes in Privacy Policy_  
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
